// Array with list of quiz questions
const questions = [{
    "question": "What does COSHH stand for?",
    "ans1": "Control of Substances Hazardous to Health",
    "ans2": "Careful of Substances Harmful to Health",
    "ans3": "Control of Spillages Hazardous to Health",
    "ans4": "Control of Substances Hurtful to Health",
    "correct": "Control of Substances Hazardous to Health"
},
{
    "question": "What are the safe systems of work, provided by an employer, designed to do??",
    "ans1": "They only help make the job quicker",
    "ans2": "They only help to stop employees having accidents",
    "ans3": "They only help stop employees and all others having accidents",
    "ans4": "They only help prevent visitors having accidents",
    "correct": "They only help stop employees and all others having accidents"
},
{
    "question": "What year did RIDDOR start?",
    "ans1": "1990",
    "ans2": "1995",
    "ans3": "2000",
    "ans4": "2005",
    "correct": "1995"
},
{
    "question": "What is the first action to take when approaching the scene of an accident?",
    "ans1": "Check for signs of life",
    "ans2": "Wait for the emergency services",
    "ans3": "Attend the most serious injury",
    "ans4": "Make sure the area is safe to enter",
    "correct":  "Make sure the area is safe to enter"
},
{
    "question": "There is a fault with the PPE, the user should:?",
    "ans1": "Not do the task and inform the supervisor of the problem immediately",
    "ans2": "Get somebody else to complete the task",
    "ans3": "Use the equipment and continue the task anyway",
    "ans4": "Use the equipment to do the task and tell the supervisor later",
    "correct": "Not do the task and inform the supervisor of the problem immediately"
},
{
    "question": "Why should accidents in the workplace be reported?",
    "ans1": "To prevent a similar accident in the future",
    "ans2": "Reduce levels of paperwork",
    "ans3": "Check whether staff are carrying out their duties or not",
    "ans4": "To enable staff to learn from their mistakes",
    "correct": "To prevent a similar accident in the future"
},
{
    "question": "Which one of the following lists contains only PPE?",
    "ans1": "Dust mask, safety goggles and ear defenders",
    "ans2": "Ear defenders, reading glasses and trainers",
    "ans3": "Thermal gloves, machine guard and overalls",
    "ans4": "Machine guard, dust mask and safety goggles",
    "correct":  "Dust mask, safety goggles and ear defenders"
},
{
    "question": "What is the best way of dealing with a hazard to ensure others are not put at risk?",
    "ans1": "Remove it immediately",
    "ans2": "Leave it for others to sort out",
    "ans3": "Place a barrier tape around it",
    "ans4": "Display a notice or warning sign",
    "correct": "Remove it immediately"
},
{
    "question": "Where should information be found regarding the disposal of old chemical products?",
    "ans1": "By contacting the manufacturer",
    "ans2": "On the product sheet or side of the container",
    "ans3": "On the internet",
    "ans4": "At the local library",
    "correct": "On the product sheet or side of the container"
},
{
    "question": "The accident book is a legal document that does what?",
    "ans1": "Describes how businesses should deal with an accident",
    "ans2": "Details risk assessments and safety rules",
    "ans3": "Records the details of an accident in the workplace",
    "ans4": "Lists the first aid requirements of the workplace",
    "correct": "Records the details of an accident in the workplace"
},
{
    "question": "Which of the following pieces of health and safety legislation is mainly concerned with the handling of hazardous materials?",
    "ans1": "Manual handling",
    "ans2": "RIDDOR",
    "ans3": "COSHH",
    "ans4": "HASAWA",
    "correct": "COSHH"
},
{
    "question": "The HASAWA applies to??",
    "ans1": "Supervisors, managers and assessors only",
    "ans2": "Trainees and supervisors only",
    "ans3": "Trainees, supervisors, managers and assessors",
    "ans4": "Trainees only",
    "correct": "Trainees, supervisors, managers and assessors"
},
{
    "question": "Which one of the following situations would be most appropriate to use PPE?",
    "ans1": "Working in the rain",
    "ans2": "Working off-site",
    "ans3": "Working indoors",
    "ans4": "Working with chemicals",
    "correct": "Working with chemicals"
},
{
    "question": "Which of the following is the best method of finding information on workshop equipment?",
    "ans1": "From the health and safety at work manual",
    "ans2": "From the manufacturer"s handbook or technical data",
    "ans3": "By discussing it with a senior colleague",
    "ans4": "By contacting the original supplier of the equipment",
    "correct": "From the manufacturer"s handbook or technical data"
},
{
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of safe working?",
    "ans1": "Lifting more than you can handle",
    "ans2": "Loading lifting equipment with as much material as possible",
    "ans3": "Wearing safety goggles to perform every task",
    "ans4": "Checking the work area to make sure it is free from hazards",
    "correct": "Checking the work area to make sure it is free from hazards"
},
{
    "question": "Which of the following statements is likely to result in an injury to the operator?",
    "ans1": "Selecting the right tool for the job",
    "ans2": "Wearing safety goggles or glasses",
    "ans3": "Using a tool with loose handles",
    "ans4": "Keeping cutting tools sharp",
    "correct": "Using a tool with loose handles"
},
{
    "question": "What is YOUR responsibility for health and safety at Work?",
    "ans1": "I have no responsbility to health and safety",
    "ans2": "I dont know, my Manager will tell me when I have a responsibility",
    "ans3": "Follow procedures and work in a safe manner",
    "ans4": "To work in a safe manner",
    "correct": "Follow procedures and work in a safe manner"
},
{
    "question": "In the event of a fire what do you do?",
    "ans1": "Leave it, somebody else will sort it.",
    "ans2": "Find a manager or teamleader and tell them, then head towards the exit",
    "ans3": "Grab the nearest fire extinguisher and tackle the fire",
    "ans4": "Walk quickly to the nearest exit and activate an alarm call button on exit",
    "correct": "Walk quickly to the nearest exit and activate an alarm call button on exit"
},
{
    "question": "What is a risk assessment?",
    "ans1": "A visual assessment made by an operator to assess risks before an operation",
    "ans2": "After an accident has occured its an used to see how it happened",
    "ans3": "A documented method of looking at work activities, considering what could go wrong, and deciding on suitable control measures to prevent loss, damage or injury in the workplace",
    "ans4": "A document made to ensure we are legally compliant",
    "correct":  "A documented method of looking at work activities, considering what could go wrong, and deciding on suitable control measures to prevent loss, damage or injury in the workplace"
},
{
    "question": "How should you lift correctly?",
    "ans1": "Adopt a stable position lift using the arms to take the weight of the lift",
    "ans2": "Adopt a stable position lift using the back to take the weight of the lift",
    "ans3": "Adopt a stable position lift using the legs to take the weight of the lift",
    "ans4": "Drag the weight so you dont need to lift it",
    "correct": "Adopt a stable position lift using the legs to take the weight of the lift"
}
];